const EthicsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What does Islam teach about honesty?",
        options: ["Not important", "Encouraged and valued", "Optional", "Discouraged"],
        correct_option: "Discouraged"
    },
    {
        question: "How does Islam view treatment of parents?",
        options: ["Critcized", "Neglected", "Respected and cared", "Ignored"],
        correct_option: "Respected and cared"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Islamic stance on kindness to animals?",
        options: ["Optional", "Not important", "Discouraged", "Encouraged"],
        correct_option: "Encouraged"
    },
    {
        question: "How does Islam view importance of forgiveness?",
        options: ["Optional", "Discouraged", "Not necessary", "Highly valued"],
        correct_option: "Highly valued"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Islam teach about helping those in need?",
        options: ["Duty", "Unnecessary", "Discouraged", "Optional"],
        correct_option: "Duty"
    },
    {
        question: "How does Islam view treatment of neighbors?",
        options: ["Avoided", "Kindness and respect", "Critcized", "Ignored"],
        correct_option: "Kindness and respect"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Islamic stance on speaking the truth?",
        options: ["Not important", "Optional", "Discouraged", "Encouraged"],
        correct_option: "Encouraged"
    },
    {
        question: "How does Islam view importance of generosity?",
        options: ["Not necessary", "Highly valued", "Discouraged", "Optional"],
        correct_option: "Highly valued"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Islam teach about respecting elders?",
        options: ["Discouraged", "Optional", "Unnecessary", "Encouraged"],
        correct_option: "Encouraged"
    },
    {
        question: "How does Islam view treatment of the environment?",
        options: ["Unnecessary", "Optional", "Important", "Discouraged"],
        correct_option: "Important"
    }
];

export default EthicsQuestions;
